







SVETLANA MOISEIENKO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Front-end developer with about 1 year of development experience. I focused on developing web applications using React/Redux

Good web design experience, which helps in the development process.

Have experience with agile methodologie (Scrum + Jira)



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MALEVICH (09.2022 - 12.2022)

Junior Front-end developer

Developed corporate websites in React to train and develop new employees in a "pass the game" format, in a senior development team.

FOTODOM (07.2022 - 08.2022)

Front-ent developer | Part time

Designed and developed a small promotional website for the company using Bootstrap as a base.

PAGO HR (05.2022 - 07.2022)

Internship

Developed a website for a charity and also managed social media.





COURSES

ûdemy

Fundamental JavaScript. With practice and projects

нетология

Fundamentals of Figma

Building a website and an application: first steps in JavaScript





STACK

- React/Redux
- Java Script
- Git Gulp • Figma
- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap





EDUCATION

I am a second year student at the Wroclaw Business Academy

Specialisation: management







LANGUAGES

- English B1 Russian native
- Polish B2 Ukrainian native







